A Finding Aid to the Polly Thayer (Starr) papers, 1846-2008, bulk 1921-2008, in the Archives of American Art AAA.thaypoll
Archives of American Art
Polly Thayer (Starr) papers
bulk 1921-2008
1846-2008
AAA.thaypoll
Archives of American Art
21.4 Linear feet
The papers of Boston portraitis and painter Polly Thayer (Starr) (1904-2006) measure 21.4 linear feet and date from 1846 to 2008, with the bulk of the materials dating from 1921-2008. The papers document Thayer’s personal life and career as a painter, portraitist, and pastel artist. Found within the papers are biographical materials, extensive family papers, correspondence with artists and art venues, interviews, writings, subject files, organization files, exhibition files, art inventory records, printed materials, five sketchbooks, artwork, and photographs.
Thayer, Polly
Arrangement note
The Polly Thayer papers were organized and inventoried by curator Dorothy Koval and other art consultants prior to arriving at the Archives of American Art, and most likely do not reflect the original order by Polly Thayer. The Archives has maintained the arrangement imposed by Koval for the bulk of the papers. This collection is arranged as 13 series.
Series 1: Biographical Material, 1921-2007 (0.8 linear feet; Box 1, 22)
Series 2: Family Files, 1846-2006 (2 linear feet; Box 1-3, 22)
Series 3: Correspondence, 1929-2008 (1.3 linear feet; Box 3-5)
Series 4: Interviews, 1995-2004 (0.2 linear feet; Box 5)
Series 5: Writings, 1922-2006 (1.7 linear feet; Box 5-6)
Series 6: Subject Files, circa 1900-2008 (3.3 linear feet; Box 7-10)
Series 7: Organization Files, 1931-2008 (1 linear feet; Box 10-11)
Series 8: Exhibition Files, 1928-2006 (1.9 linear feet; Box 11-13)
Series 9: Art Inventory, circa 1940-1999 (4.6 linear feet; Box 13-17)
Series 10: Printed Material, 1900-2006 (1.8 linear feet; Box 17-19, 22)
Series 11: Sketchbooks, 1930-circa 1970 (0.3 linear feet; Box 19, 23)
Series 12: Artwork, 1927-circa 1990 (0.4 linear feet; Box 19, 23, OV 25)
Series 13: Photographs, 1898-2006 (2.1 linear feet; Box 19-21, 24)
Scope and Contents note
The papers of Boston portraitist and painter Polly Thayer (Starr) (1904-2006) measure 21.4 linear feet and date from 1846 to 2008, with the bulk of the materials dating from 1921-2008. The papers document Thayer’s personal life and career as a painter, portraitist, and pastel artist. Found within the papers are biographical materials, extensive family papers, correspondence with artists and art venues, interviews, writings, subject files, organization files, exhibition files, art inventory records, printed materials, five sketchbooks, artwork, and photographs.
Biographical material includes a marriage certificate, school records, inventories of possessions, passports, files about the 1923 Great Kanto earthquake in Japan, and a few personal and scattered financial documents such as invoices and receipts for various art related expenses.
Extensive family papers on many of Polly Thayer’s immediate and extended family members include obituaries, condolence letters, writings, and printed materials. The most voluminous files are about Polly Thayer’s husband Donald Carter Starr, her mother Ethel Randolph Thayer, and her father Ezra Ripley Thayer.
There is limited correspondence with friends and and colleagues, including Royal Cortissoz, Philip Hofer, Tasha Tudor (photocopies), Dorothy Koval, the curator who wrote about Thayer for her first show at Vose Galleries in 2001, as well as two art consultants who helped Thayer inventory her artwork. The bulk of the correspondence is with museums, galleries, and other venues such as the Boston Museum of Fine Arts, Copley Society of Boston, and Vose Galleries.
Interviews with Polly Thayer include transcripts as well as sound and video recordings. There is also a sound recording of poet and professor Doris Abramson discussing Catherine Sargent Huntington.
Writings include typescript and handwritten drafts of essays, notebooks, and notes on assorted topics. The bulk of the material was written by Thayer, with a few writings by others.
Subject files are found for people and general interests. The "People" files are collected documents about Thayer's friends, colleagues, artists, and portrait subjects. The files include short biographies, articles, obituaries, a few photographs, two videocassettes and one sound recording. The most voluminous files are on Francis DeLancey Cunningham, the Howe family, Rose Nichols, May Sarton, John Brooks Wheelwright, and Agnes Yarnall. Thayer's “Interests” files consist of articles and clippings on various topics such as animals, humor, and pacifism.
Organization files contain materials related to Polly Thayer’s charitable contributions, club memberships and affiliations, including The Chilton Club, Nucleus Club, Religious Society of Friends, and Trustees of Reservations, among others. These files contain seven sound recordings.
Exhibition files contain exhibition catalogs, reviews, clippings, notes, inventory price lists, and other materials about Thayer’s solo and group shows.
Art inventory records consist of dismantled binders of inventories that also include photographs of artwork and descriptive information such as the title, medium, and dimensions. There are also photographic inventories of works of art arranged by subject, and several partial art inventories.
Printed materials include two scrapbooks compiled by Polly Thayer’s mother containing articles about Thayer, magazines, journals, exhibition catalogs, brochures, exhibition invitations, postcards, clippings, and miscellaneous materials.
Five sketchbooks include figure drawings, portrait sketches, and landscape sketches. Also found are loose drawings of animals, landscapes, and people.
Disbound binders of photographs contain images of works of art that are grouped by subject, including portraits, landscapes, and “mystical/flowers/animals," as well as personal photographs of Polly Thayer and family members, houses, social events, pets, and friends. There is one small disbound photograph album of houses and properties.
Biographical/Historical note
Polly Thayer (Starr) (1904-2006) was a Boston painter of portraits, landscapes, and still lifes.
Ethel Randolph Thayer, known as Polly, was born in Boston in 1904, the daughter of Professor Ezra Ripley Thayer, also Dean of the Harvard Law School, and Ethel Randolph Thayer, née Clark. Thayer began her drawing lessons at an early age and later attended the Westover Boarding School in Middlebury, Connecticut. Although she signed some of her early paintings Ethel Thayer, by the end of the 1920s she generally signed her work Polly Thayer. She continued to use Polly Thayer as her brush name after she married, although in 1967 she changed her name legally from Ethel Randolph Starr to Polly Thayer Starr.
After graduating from Westover School, Thayer traveled to China, Korea, and Japan with her brother and mother. While in Japan, the Great Kanto Earthquake of 1923 struck just as their ship was about to leave Yokohama. In the devastation that followed, their ship was used as a hospital and Polly Thayer assisted with nursing the injured.
After returning home, Thayer began her formal studies at the Boston Museum of Fine Arts from 1923 to 1925 where she took painting classes taught by Philip Hale. She eventually left the Boston Museum and began private painting lessons with Hale. While working under Hale, she painted a large nude, Circles, which was awarded the National Academy of Design’s coveted Julius Hallgarten Prize in 1929. She also spent the summer of 1924 in Provincetown studying with Charles Hawthorne and traveled to Europe where she studied at the Académie Colarossi in Paris. She later studied in Madrid and, from 1930-1933, at the Art Students League in New York City.
Thayer’s first solo exhibition was held on New Year’s Eve, 1930 at the Doll & Richards gallery in Boston. The Globe reviewer declared it “surely settles her status as one of the foremost painters in the country.” The success of the exhibition led to numerous portrait commissions –many of them exhibited at Wildenstein gallery in New York City – and launched Thayer’s career as a portrait artist. Her portrait subjects include Judith Anderson, Jacques Barzun, Maurice Evans, Lewis Galantiere, Robert Hale, May Sarton, John Wheelwright, and Agnes Yarnall, among others. Additional galleries that subsequently gave Thayer solo shows were the Sessler Gallery in Philadelphia; Contemporary Arts and Pietrantonio Galleries in New York; and in Boston the Guild of Boston Artists, Grace Horne Galleries, Child’s Gallery, The Copley Society, the St. Botolph Club and the Boston Public Library.
In 1933, Polly Thayer married Donald Starr, a Boston lawyer and avid sailor. They married in Italy and honeymooned in Paris while he took a break from a sailing trip around the world on his schooner “Pilgrim.” They had two daughters, Victoria and Dinah. In 1942 Thayer joined the Society of Friends (Quakers) which became an important part of her life and identity. She was active in many educational, charitable and cultural institutions and local clubs. Thayer had long been fascinated by the dynamics, meaning and variety of visual experience. In 1981 the Friends Journal published her essay “On Seeing,” a paper she continued to refine until she was ninety-seven.
In the 1950s and 1960s, Polly Thayer began focusing more on landscapes and still lifes and continued to be prolific artist, exhibiting in numerous solo and group exhibits in Boston, New York, and Philadelphia. In her later years she renewed an early affiliation with Vose Galleries which she maintained for the rest of her life. In 2001, she was the only living artist whose work was included in the Boston Museum of Fine Arts exhibition "A Studio of Her Own" and a banner of her portrait of May Sarton hung over the entrance to the Museum.
Polly Thayer (Starr) died on August 30, 2006.
Conditions Governing Access note
Use of original papers requires an appointment. Use of archival audiovisual recordings with no duplicate access copy requires advance notice.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The Polly Thayer (Starr) papers were donated to the Archives of American Art by Polly Thayer in 1998 and again in 2008 by Thayer via Stephanie S. Wright, executor.
Related Archival Materials note
The Archives of American Art also holds an oral history interview of Polly Thayer conducted May 12, 1995-February 1, 1996, by Robert F. Brown.
The Polly Thayer Starr Charitable Trust holds archival materials and artwork by Polly Thayer.
Abramson, Doris E.; Copley Society. (Boston, Mass.); Cortissoz, Royal, 1869-1948; Friends General Conference. (U.S.); Hofer, Philip, 1898-1984; Koval, Dorothy; Museum of Fine Arts, Boston; Nucleus Club. (Boston, Mass.); Sarton, May, 1912-; Starr, Donald C.; Thayer, Ethel Randolph, 1870-1953; Thayer, Ezra Ripley, 1866-1915; Trustees of Reservations. (Mass.); Tudor, Tasha; Vose Galleries of Boston; Wheelwright, John, 1897-1940; Yarnall, Agnes; Drawings; Interviews; Kanto Earthquake, Japan, 1923; Painters -- Massachusetts -- Boston; Photographs; Portrait painters; Scrapbooks; Sketchbooks; Sketches; Sound recordings; Transcripts; Video recordings; Women artists
- Biographical Material, 1921-2007; Series 1; 0.8 Linear feet Box 1, 22
  Scope and Contents note
  Biographical material includes Polly Thayer's school records, marriage certificate, inventories of possessions meant for appraisal at houses she owned, journal entries and clippings about the 1923 Great Kanto earthquake from Thayer's trip to Japan, and passports. Also included are financial documents on art-related expenses such as invoices and receipts for framing, printing, and conservation, in addition to inventories created by Dorothy Koval for her reference and research of Thayer's papers prior to their arrival at the archives. Some of Koval's inventories are on 2 electronic discs (CD).
  - Westover School Records and Reunion Material, 1921; 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Great Kanto Earthquake (Box 1)
    - Polly Thayer's Travel Journal, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Writings by Mother Ethel Thayer, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Printed Materials, 1923-2004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - United Kingdom Certificate if Registration for Travel, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Weir River Farm Property Management, 1931-2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Marriage Certificate from Genoa, Italy, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Metal Engraving for Calling Card, circa 1935 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Check Stubs and Deposit Slips, 1937-1939 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 198 Beacon Street Inventory and Appraisal of Contents, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Notes and Records on Vision Loss, 1952; 1981-2005 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Agamemnon Program and Related Materials, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Visitor's Pass to View Egyptian Monuments, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Memorial and Obituary Plans, 1976-2006 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - West Chop Summer House Inventory of Contents, circa 1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 90th Birthday Tribute Signed by Members of Cambridge Friends Meeting, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Oversized material housed in Box 22, Folder 1.
  - Brookhaven Retirement Home Assorted Materials, 1996-2006 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Resumes, circa 2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Passports, 1925-1934 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Passports, 1955-1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Passports, 1977-1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Invoices and Receipts for Framing Artwork, 1945-2005 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Invoices and Receipts for Photography, 1976-2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Invoices and Receipts for Printing, 1992-2001 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Invoices and Receipts for Art Conservation, 1993-2004 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Invoices and Receipts for Shipping, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Dorothy Koval's Inventory of Thayer's Papers, circa 2004 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Dorothy Koval's Inventory of Thayer's Papers, 2007; 2 Electronic discs (CD) (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Oversized Birthday Tribute Card from Box 1, Folder 16, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Family Files, 1846-2006; Series 2; 2 Linear feet Box 1-3, 22
  Arrangement note
  Family files on the members of the Starr and Thayer family are arranged alphabetically. Found at the end of the series are a few folders on extended family and relatives, including the Clarks, Ripleys and Vintons, all of which are arranged alphabetically. Miscelleanous folders about genealogy are arranged at the end of the series.
  Polly Thayer's family files, which include immediate and extended family, are extensive. Several individuals, such as Thayer's parents, Ezra Ripley Thayer and Ethel Randolph Thayer (née Clark), and her husband Donald Carter Starr, have multiple folders. Since there are files on members from the maternal and paternal sides of Thayer's family tree, there are materials on the Clark, Ripley and Vinton families, in addition to the voluminous folders on the Thayers and Starrs. The series includes correspondence, writings, printed materials, condolence letters, memorial plans, estate papers, and obituaries.
  - Starr, Donald Carter (Box 1)
    - Short Biographies, 1920-1992 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Passports, 1926-1935 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Passports, 1960-1987 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Harvard Reunion Runes, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - National Geographic Article about Schooner Pilgrim, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Typescript Draft of Article "Vanished Signs of Vanished Times", 1983 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Typescript Draft about Charitable Giving, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - St. Botolph Club Donations, 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - St. Botolph Club Donations, 1996-2006 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Assorted Notes and Sketches, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Funeral Arrangements, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Obituaries, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Inventory of Writings, circa 1992 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Starr, Donald Carter, Continued (Box 2)
    - Condolence Letters, A-L, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Condolence Letters, M-Z, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Starr's Miscellany Table of Contents, circa 1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Memorial Services, 1992-2006 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence about Boats, 1992-2006 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Schooner Pilgrim's Progress Editing Process, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Schooner Pilgrim's Progress Correspondence with David Ford, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Schooner Pilgrim's Progress Correspondence with Donald S. Marshall, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Schooner Pilgrim's Progress Cover Design, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Schooner Pilgrim's Progress Book Reviews, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Schooner Pilgrim's Progress Letters from Readers, 1996-2004 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Schooner Pilgrim's Progress Chapters Read by Richard Dey, circa 1997; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Inventory of Paintings and Drawings, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Starr, Victoria Thayer (Box 2)
    - Baby Book, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Babysitting Notes by Childhood Nurse Sally, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Vocabulary List, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Childhood Compositions and Drawings, circa 1948 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - "Cartoons of Vicky's Mastectomy, 1985, Chinon" (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Postcard of Polly Thayer's Drawing Victoria with Hamster, circa 1991 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Bryn Mawr Alumnae Bulletin, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Photocopy of Diplome d' honneur for Restoration of French Building, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Higham House Restoration, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous Printed Materials, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Thayer, Eleanor Arnold (Box 2)
    - Postcard, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Writings, 1913-1919 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - News Clippings, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Memorial and Obituary, 1923-1957 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Thayer, Ethel Randolph (Box 2)
    - Letters from Phillips Brooks, 1885-1891 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Letters from Joseph Trumbull Stickney, 1893-1895 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Letter from President William Howard Taft, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1885-1957 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - "Servants" Book, 1898-1950 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      A notebook containing the names of servants, their dates of service, and notes about their quality of work.
    - Shopping List and Recipe Notes, 1902 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Locks of Children's Hair, circa 1910 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Will and Estate Papers, 1923-1959 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Typescript Drafts of Open Letters, circa 1938 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Writings on Religion and the Oxford Group, circa 1938 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - News Clippings, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Handwriting Analysis, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Memorial Service, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Condolence Letters, 1959-1982 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Family Service of Greater Boston Charity, 1986-2003 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Thayer, Ezra Ripley (Box 2)
    - Travel Diary, 1882-1883 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - The Harvard Monthly, 1888 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Typed Excerpts of Letters to Ethel Thayer, 1910-1911 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      Transcriptions of selected letters, sometimes partial and sometimes in full, written by Ezra Thayer to his wife Ethel Thayer over the course of a trip.
  - Thayer, Ezra Ripley, Continued (Box 3)
    - News Clippings, 1913-2001 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Typescript Draft of "A Sketch of Thayer's Life" and a copy of Ezra Ripley Thayer published by Harvard Law School, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Harvard Law School Class of 1914: The Third Class Report, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Memorials, 1961-2004 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Ezra Ripley Thayer Fellowship at Harvard, 1973-2003 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - "Ezra Ripley Thayer: Dean of Harvard Law School 1910-1915", 2002 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Thayer, James Bradley, the elder (Box 3)
    - Obituaries, 1902 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Journal of Legal Education, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Jay Hook's Research and Thesis on James Bradley Thayer, 1987-1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Harvard Law School Special Collections Records, 1987-2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - "Digging for Roots: The North Dakota Constitution and the Thayer Correspondence", 1989 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Photocopy of Journal Entry, circa 1990 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Northwestern University Centennial, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Thayer, James Bradley, the younger (Box 3)
    - Harvard Law School Donation and Records, 1982-2000 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Estate Papers, 1982-1991 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Thayer, Sophia Bradley (Box 3)
    - Obituary, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Condolence Letters, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Thayer, Theodora W. (Box 3)
    - Letter to Mary Vinton Clark, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Condolence Letters, 1905 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Articles and News Clippings, 1906-2005 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Thayer, William Sydney, Articles and News Clippings, 1932-1985 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Clark, Mary Vinton, Estate Papers, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Oversized material housed in Box 22, Folder 2
  - Emerson, Mary Moody, Biographical Sketches, circa 2000 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Ripley, Ezra, Biographical Sketches, circa 1990 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Ripley, Samuel (Box 3)
    - Letter to Parish Members, 1846 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Reverend Samuel Ripley of Waltham, 1897 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Ripley, Sarah Alden, Biographical Sketches, 1973-1999 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Ripley and Thayer Family Genealogy Charts, circa 1980 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Ripley and Thayer Family, Old Manse Historic Building, 1983-2004 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Vinton Family, 1969-1987 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous Family Material, 1948-1983 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Oversized Estate Papers from Box 3, Folder 22, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1929-2008; Series 3; 1.3 Linear feet Box 3-5
  This series is arranged as 2 subseries.
  3.1: Friends and Colleagues, 1929-2008
  3.2: Galleries, Museums, Venues, 1940-2006
  This series contains correspondence with friends and colleagues as well as correspondence with museums, galleries, and arts venues.
  - Friends and Colleagues, 1929-2008; 3.1
    Following the first file on family history, the files are arranged alphabetically by correspondent with unidentified correspondence at the end of the series.
    Correspondence with friends and colleagues is limited. Notable correspondents include Royal Cortissoz, Philip Hofer, Louis Kronenberger, Anne Parrish, and photocopies of letters from Tasha Tudor. The most voluminous folders of correspondence are from curator Dorothy Koval, as well as Wendy Swanton and Margaret Winslow, art consultants who helped organize Thayer's artwork before the Archives received the collection. There are a few letters of inquiry about Polly Thayer's family history for genealogical research from researchers and assorted correspondents.
    - Correspondence about Family History, 1972-1983 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Apthorp, L. L., circa 1934 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Arapoff, Alexis, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - A Miscellaneous, 1977-2005 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Barzun, Jacques, circa 1933-1944 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Blackman, Joyce, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Bliss, Josselyn, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - B Miscellaneous, 1993-2004 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Coolidge, John G., 1931-1932 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Cortissoz, Royal, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - C-E Miscellaneous, circa 1935-2001 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Fullery Family, circa 1945-1993 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - F-G Miscellaneous, 1931-2001 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Harrison, Marie L., circa 1958 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Hodges, Eloise, 1973-circa 1995 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Hofer, Philip, 1950-1974 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Howe, Mark A. DeWolfe, 1937; 1987-1988 (Box 3)
    - H Miscellaneous, circa 1933-2003 (Box 3, Folder 49)